v1 gemini-1.5-flash: models/gemini-1.5-flash is not found for API version v1, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported methods.
v1 gemini-1.5-pro: models/gemini-1.5-pro is not found for API version v1, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported methods.
v1 gemini-2.0-flash-exp: models/gemini-2.0-flash-exp is not found for API version v1, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported methods.
v1 gemini-1.5-flash-latest: models/gemini-1.5-flash-latest is not found for API version v1, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported methods.
v1beta gemini-1.5-flash: models/gemini-1.5-flash is not found for API version v1beta, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported methods.
v1beta gemini-1.5-pro: models/gemini-1.5-pro is not found for API version v1beta, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported methods.
v1beta gemini-2.0-flash-exp: models/gemini-2.0-flash-exp is not found for API version v1beta, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported methods.
v1beta gemini-1.5-flash-latest: models/gemini-1.5-flash-latest is not found for API version v1beta, or is not supported for generateContent. Call ListModels to see the list of available models and their supported methods.
